

# Rekam Sari

# **Contact**

- 089523486210
- rekamsari8@gmail.com
- North Jakarta, Indonesia
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/rekam-sari-9b094413a/
- **⊞** 12 JUNE 1996
- Married

### **Protofolio**

https://rekamsari5.github.io

# **Technical Skills**

PHP, Javascript, PWA, Python, NodeJS, MySQL, Linux, WordPress, Materialize, Codelgniter Framework, Bootstrap 4, Oracle Database, Unifed Modeling Language (UML), VISIO, Figma.

### **Education**

Gunadarma University (2014 - 2018)

Department of Information Systems Faculty of Computer Science (GPA 3.53)

- Bachelor Thesis: Development of Information System for Management of Intellectual Property Rights Subdivision of Copyright at Gunadarma University Based on the Website.
  - Date Created: 14 August 2018.
- **Scientific writing:** Website-Based Islamic Study Schedule Information.
  - o Date Created: 26 July 2017

### **About**

My background is Computer Science with a specialization in Software Engineering. In my career I have completed several internal projects for internals (e.g., operations, inventory, and a bit of data analyst). I love working within a dynamic and diverse environment where I can contribute my creativity, strong interpersonal skills, as well as my eagerness to grow.

# **Work Experience**

### System Analyst PT.Margacipta Wirasentosa

Tangerang, May 2021 - December 2021

- Interact with other departments to find out their needs.
- Analyzing Application systems and creating flowcharts.
- Trial & error system application.
- Create an executable manual system.
- Balanced Scorecard (BSC) data analysis IT department reports
- Trainers
- Analysis of the timeline of the system analyst division
- Divisional ISO audit data analysis

# Information Technology Specialist PT BPR Kredit Mandiri Indonesia

Tangerang, November 2020 - May 2021

- Developed a front-end system for assets document with the Codelgniter Web Framework.
- Developed a full-stack system for BSS receipt numbers with the Codelgniter Web Framework.

# Full-stack Developer PT. Say Grow Indonesia (Growpal)

Jakarta, April 2019 - August 2020

- Implement a Single Page Application (SPA) and RESTful API to develop some internal services (web application).
- Setup, manage, deploy, and monitor servers to ensure business continuity and production services is running well using Digital Ocean and Ubuntu server 16/18.04

# Organizational Experience

 BEM FIKTI (Faculty of Computer Science & Information Technology) UNIVERSITY GUNADARMA (2015–2016) as Community Service Staff.

# Courses & Workshops

- Mini Class Intro To Golang for Beginner (Coding.ID)
- Python Fundamental for Data Science (DQLAB)
- Introduction to Data Science with Python (DQLAB)
- Fundamental DBMS (Gunadarma University)
- Java Programming Language (Gunadarma University)
- Oracle for Intermediate (Gunadarma University)
- SQL Server for Intermediate (Gunadarma University)
- Oracle Project (Gunadarma University)

# <u>Languages</u>

English : PassiveIndonesia : Active

- Developed front-end and back-end systems to provide sentiment and non-sentiment information on fisheries news from various news site sources. (code name: lib.growpal)
- Implement Realtime Applications with Puppeteer NodeJS and Cron Jobs on Linux for scraping web data from websites (Tokopedia).
- Analyze Shrimp trend data with Python.
- Developed a system web ecommerce with Plugin ecommerce WordPress. (code name: Shop Growbuy).
- Developed a front-end system for digitizing as well as providing information about the purchase of property and equipment (fixed asset). (code name: Growpal Asset Management).
- Tech-stack: PHP, Javascript, PWA, Python, NodeJS, Nginx, MySQL, Linux, Wordpress, Materialize.

### **Back-end Developer**

### PT. Cranium Royal Aditama

Jakarta, October 2018 - December 2018

- Developed a back-end system for product admins with the Codelgniter Web Framework.
- Tech-stack: Codelgniter Framework, PHP, Javascript, MySQL, Bootstrap 4.

### Full-stack Developer

#### PT. I APP Software House Solutions

Jakarta, November 2017 - June 2018

- Developed a back-end system for product admins with the Codelgniter Web Framework.
- Tech-stack: Codelgniter Framework, PHP, Javascript, MySQL, Bootstrap 4.

#### Lab Assistant

#### **Gunadarma University**

Depok, September 2015 - October 2018

- Trainer for Oracle Database Beginners at Gunadarma University.
- Tech-stack: Oracle Database.